<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Database>
	<EnglishText>

        <!-- city names -->
        <Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_ZHOU_CHINA1" >
        <Text>HAOJING</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_ZHOU_CHINA10" >
        <Text>YU</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_ZHOU_CHINA11" >
        <Text>WU</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_ZHOU_CHINA12" >
        <Text>ZHENG</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_ZHOU_CHINA13" >
        <Text>SUI</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_ZHOU_CHINA14" >
        <Text>LU</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_ZHOU_CHINA15" >
        <Text>XING</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_ZHOU_CHINA16" >
        <Text>CAI</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_ZHOU_CHINA17" >
        <Text>CAO</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_ZHOU_CHINA18" >
        <Text>ZHAO</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_ZHOU_CHINA19" >
        <Text>LUO</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_ZHOU_CHINA2" >
        <Text>WEI</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_ZHOU_CHINA20" >
        <Text>LIRONG</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_ZHOU_CHINA21" >
        <Text>SU</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_ZHOU_CHINA22" >
        <Text>CHU</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_ZHOU_CHINA23" >
        <Text>ZHAO</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_ZHOU_CHINA24" >
        <Text>YAN</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_ZHOU_CHINA25" >
        <Text>WEI</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_ZHOU_CHINA26" >
        <Text>HAN</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_ZHOU_CHINA27" >
        <Text>JIN</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_ZHOU_CHINA28" >
        <Text>HU</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_ZHOU_CHINA29" >
        <Text>QI</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_ZHOU_CHINA3" >
        <Text>SHEN</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_ZHOU_CHINA30" >
        <Text>XU</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_ZHOU_CHINA4" >
        <Text>CHEN</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_ZHOU_CHINA5" >
        <Text>QI</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_ZHOU_CHINA6" >
        <Text>YUE</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_ZHOU_CHINA7" >
        <Text>SONG</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_ZHOU_CHINA8" >
        <Text>Gija Joseon</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_ZHOU_CHINA9" >
        <Text>QIN</Text>
        </Row>

        <!-- citizen names -->
        <Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_ZHOU_CHINA_FEMALE_1" >
        <Text>Tai Jiang</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_ZHOU_CHINA_FEMALE_10" >
        <Text>Tai Ren</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_ZHOU_CHINA_FEMALE_2" >
        <Text>Tai Si</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_ZHOU_CHINA_FEMALE_3" >
        <Text>Yi Jiang</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_ZHOU_CHINA_FEMALE_4" >
        <Text>Ding Jiang</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_ZHOU_CHINA_FEMALE_5" >
        <Text>Meng's Mother</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_ZHOU_CHINA_FEMALE_6" >
        <Text>XiJun's Wife</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_ZHOU_CHINA_FEMALE_7" >
        <Text>QiJiang Of JinWen</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_ZHOU_CHINA_FEMALE_8" >
        <Text>XuMu's Wife</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_ZHOU_CHINA_FEMALE_9" >
        <Text>The daughter of the man who wounded the locust tree</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_ZHOU_CHINA_MALE_1" >
        <Text>Confucius</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_ZHOU_CHINA_MALE_10" >
        <Text>Mencius</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_ZHOU_CHINA_MALE_2" >
        <Text>Xun Kuang</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_ZHOU_CHINA_MALE_3" >
        <Text>Laozi</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_ZHOU_CHINA_MALE_4" >
        <Text>Zhuangzi</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_ZHOU_CHINA_MALE_5" >
        <Text>Mozi</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_ZHOU_CHINA_MALE_6" >
        <Text>Sun Wu</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_ZHOU_CHINA_MALE_7" >
        <Text>Zou Yan</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_ZHOU_CHINA_MALE_8" >
        <Text>Su Qin</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_ZHOU_CHINA_MALE_9" >
        <Text>Xu Xing</Text>
        </Row>

        <!-- civilization -->
        <Row Tag="LOC_CIVILIZATION_ZHOU_CHINA_ADJECTIVE" >
        <Text>Zhou</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_CIVILIZATION_ZHOU_CHINA_FULLNAME" >
        <Text>Zhou Empire</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_CIVILIZATION_ZHOU_CHINA_NAME" >
        <Text>Zhou</Text>
        </Row>

        
        <Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_PAGE_CIVILIZATION_ZHOU_CHINA_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" >
            <Text>The Zhou people are an ancient tribe living in the area of the present-day Shaanxi-Gansu Loess Plateau and the Weishui Basin, and it is said that the surname is Ji because of "Ji Shui". According to legend, the ancestor of Zhou was born to Jiang Yan of the Tai family, and was also known as Houji because he was good at farming. The ancestors of the Zhou people were probably a branch of the Qiang people. In the early years of the Shang Dynasty, Houji's descendant Gong Liu led the people to move from Tai to Ci. In the early days, the Zhou people lived in the Wugong area of Shaanxi, and by the time of Gongliu, the Zhou tribe had moved to Feng. It gradually changed from a farming tribe to a city dominated by farming. Since Gong Liu, and through the ninth generation, when Gu Gong's father was the head of the tribe, the Zhou people were persecuted by the invasion of Xun Yurong and had to migrate. They crossed the Qi, Fu and Liang Mountains and moved to Zhouyuan, south of Qishan in the Wei River Valley.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_PAGE_CIVILIZATION_ZHOU_CHINA_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_2" >
            <Text>Zhouyuan is rich in products, fertile land, convenient irrigation, superior farming conditions, and rapid economic development. After moving to the Zhou Yuan, the Zhou people became subjects of the Dayi Shang and accepted the culture and writing of the Shang Dynasty. Gu Gong's father passed on the throne Ji Li, Ji Li not only married with the nobles of the Shang Dynasty, but also was named a "priest" by the Shang King Wending, becoming the most important uncle of the Shang Dynasty in the West. At this time, Zhou was already a powerful state under the Shang Dynasty. Despite their close relationship, the Shang Dynasty was always on the lookout for this new force.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_PAGE_CIVILIZATION_ZHOU_CHINA_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_3" >
            <Text>After Xibo Jichang succeeded to the throne, the national strength was insufficient to confront Shang, so he continued to submit to Shang and became Shang Xibo. But Yin Shang was not at ease with Zhou. Di Xin once imprisoned Ji Chang in Jinli, and killed his son as a broth, forcing King Wen to drink it. The Zhou people bribed Di Xin with a BMW and a beautiful woman to get King Wen free. After King Wen returned to China, his heart for business did not slacken. On the one hand, he strengthened the strength of the Zhou people and made some tribes near the Zhou State annexed. On the other hand, it is carrying out military expansion. After the crusade against Misu, Chongguo and other countries, the capital was moved to Fengdu (now the west bank of the Feng River in Huxian County, Xi An City, Shaanxi Province), preparing to enter the Yin Shang.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_PAGE_CIVILIZATION_ZHOU_CHINA_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_4" >
            <Text>King Wen died, the second son Ji Fa ascended the throne called King Wu of Zhou, on the east bank of the Feng River, and built the pickaxe Beijing, Feng Ho and the two capitals face each other across the water, there are bridges to connect, and called Feng Ho City. In the 11th century BC, he led 300 chariots, 3,000 tigers, 45,000 armor soldiers and 170,000 troops of the Shang Dynasty to fight in Muye (now Ji County, Henan). King Wu of Zhou fell, the former disciples defected in the battle of Muye, the Zhou army won a great victory, and the king of Shang set himself on fire in Lutai with jewels and jade on his back. The Shang Dynasty died, because the Zhou tribe moved to Zhou Yuan when the ancient prince was father, and after King Wu destroyed Yin, he took "Zhou" as the name of the dynasty, and the Zhou Dynasty was established.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_PAGE_CIVILIZATION_ZHOU_CHINA_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_5" >
            <Text>In the early years of the Western Zhou Dynasty, Zhou Tianzi established vassal states in various places through the "feudal statehood", canonized the same surname, the previous emperors and meritorious heroes, and at the same time passed a series of regulations on the power of the Son of Heaven and the obligations of the princes, forming the power distribution and operation mechanism between the Son of Heaven and the princes. In addition, the Western Zhou Dynasty formulated and implemented a complete set of hierarchical ritual systems to strengthen the hierarchical subordination relationship between various levels of government under the feudal system, thus establishing a ritual order of "ritual and music conquest from the Son of Heaven". After the vassal states of the Western Zhou Dynasty were subject to feudal statehood, they implemented a unified social system with the Western Zhou Dynasty, including the feudal system, the patriarchal system, the Jingtian system, and the Guoye system. The establishment of the relationship between the emperor and the princes and ministers of the Western Zhou Dynasty, the strengthening of the subordinate relationship between the power of the vassal states and the Zhou royal family, and the formation of a unified order of etiquette and governance marked the initial formation of a new type of state government in Chinese history, the Great Unified State Government.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_PAGE_CIVILIZATION_ZHOU_CHINA_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_6" >
            <Text>In 770 BC, King Ping of Zhou moved east to Luoyi (now Luoyang, Henan), marking the beginning of the Eastern Zhou Dynasty. Since the Eastern Zhou Dynasty, the Zhou Dynasty has turned from strong to weak, the royal family has been declining day by day, and the power has fallen. The vassal states fought against each other, and wars were frequent. Small vassal states were annexed one after another, and powerful vassal states achieved local unification and supremacy. In 453 BC, Han, Zhao, and Wei overthrew the Zhi clan, and the three families were divided. In 403 BC, King Weilie of Zhou canonized Sanjin as princes; In 386 BC, Tian He was listed as a prince, and the pattern of the Seven Heroes of the Warring States was formally formed.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_PAGE_CIVILIZATION_ZHOU_CHINA_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_7" >
            <Text>With the construction of water conservancy, the use of iron tools and the spread of cattle farming, and the development of commerce and currency, the economy of the vassal states developed in the middle and late Spring and Autumn periods, and the political situation also changed accordingly. The power of the ministers and doctors in the vassal states gradually developed. These developments have also brought about changes in the structure of society. The hereditary hierarchy was dismantled, and some of the former nobility lost their status, while others of the time became rich through business or other opportunities, and even became prominent figures in the political group. The bureaucracy has changed.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_PAGE_CIVILIZATION_ZHOU_CHINA_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_8" >
            <Text>In the face of this kind of etiquette collapse and social changes, various vassal states have changed their laws and recruited talents. Scholars or thinkers representing all classes, strata, and political forces all attempt to explain or put forward propositions about the universe, society, and everything in accordance with the interests and demands of their own class (layer) or group. They wrote books and lectures, recruited disciples, talked loudly, and criticized each other, so that a situation of "a hundred schools of thought contending" appeared in the ideological field.</Text>
        </Row>


        <Row Tag="LOC_TRAIT_ZHOU_CHINA_ABILITY_DESCRIPTION" >
            <Text>[LIST][LI][B]Culture Buildings[/B] gain [B]+2[icon:YIELD_CULTURE] Culture[/B] and [B]+2[icon:YIELD_HAPPINESS] Happiness Adjacency for Quarters.[/B][LI][B]+30% [icon:YIELD_PRODUCTION] Production [/B]towards constructing [B]Weiyang Palace[/B].[/LIST]</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_TRAIT_ZHOU_CHINA_ABILITY_NAME" >
        <Text>Zhou Li</Text>
        </Row>

        <Row Tag="LOC_MOD_ZHOU_CULTURE_BUILDING_URBAN_CULTURE_ADJACENCY_DESCRIPTION" >
        <Text>Culture Buildings gain a +2[icon:YIELD_CULTURE] Culture Adjacency for Quarters.</Text>
        </Row>

        <Row Tag="LOC_MOD_ZHOU_CULTURE_BUILDING_URBAN_HAPPINESS_ADJACENCY_DESCRIPTION" >
        <Text>Culture Buildings gain a +2[icon:YIELD_HAPPINESS] Happiness Adjacency for Quarters.</Text>
        </Row>

        <Row Tag="LOC_MOD_CIV_WONDER_PRODUCTION_ZHOU_CHINA_DESCRIPTION" >
        <Text>+30% [icon:YIELD_PRODUCTION] Production from being Zhou's associated Wonder.</Text>
        </Row>

        <!-- buildings -->
        <Row Tag="LOC_BUILDING_BIYONG_NAME" >
        <Text>Biyong</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_BUILDING_BIYONG_DESCRIPTION" >
        <Text>+3[icon:YIELD_CULTURE] Culture. +1[icon:YIELD_CULTURE] Culture Adjacency for Quarters and Wonders. +15%[icon:YIELD_PRODUCTION] Production towards training Cavalry and Ranged Units in this City. Zhou Unique Culture Building. Ageless. </Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_BUILDING_BIYONG_TOOLTIP" >
        <Text>+15%[icon:YIELD_PRODUCTION] Production towards training Cavalry and Ranged Units in this City. Zhou Unique Culture Building. Ageless.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_BUILDING_ZONGMIAO_NAME" >
        <Text>Zongmiao</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_BUILDING_ZONGMIAO_DESCRIPTION" >
        <Text>+3[icon:YIELD_HAPPINESS] Happiness. +1[icon:YIELD_DIPLOMACY] Diplomacy Adjacency for Quarters and Wonders. Zhou Unique Happiness Building. Ageless.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_BUILDING_ZONGMIAO_TOOLTIP" >
        <Text>Zhou Unique Happiness Building. Ageless.</Text>
        </Row>

        <Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_PAGE_BUILDING_BIYONG_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" >
        <Text>Biyong, also known as the university, is an important ceremonial building that lasted from the pre-Qin period to the Ming and Qing dynasties. According to the "Book of Han": "The Duke of Zhou assisted the king, the way of King was quite harmonious, the ceremony was formulated, the place where the Son of Heaven worshiped the sky was called Mingtang and Biyong, and the place where the princes perform sacrifices was called Pan Palace." According to the literature, Biyong is supposed to be a complex of buildings with an island in the middle (with a main building) and surrounded by water, which looks like a ring-shaped jade.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_PAGE_BUILDING_BIYONG_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_2" >
        <Text>As an important ceremonial building and palace education facility in the Western Zhou Dynasty, Biyong mainly has the following characteristics: first, Piyong in the Western Zhou Dynasty was built in the suburbs, surrounded by pools, and there were hall-like thatched houses on the middle highland, and there were vast gardens nearby. There are birds and beasts in the garden, and fish and turtles in the pool. Second, the Western Zhou Biyong was not only a place for the children of the nobles to study, but also a place for the members of the nobility to salute, assemble, eat, practice martial arts, and play music, and had the nature of an auditorium, a conference room, a club and a sports field, which was actually a place for the public activities of the nobles at that time, including sports. Third, the teaching content of Piyong in the Western Zhou Dynasty was mainly based on ritual music and archery, and the Western Zhou Dynasty was a ceremonial society, and the study of ritual music was part of the daily life of the aristocracy.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_PAGE_BUILDING_ZONGMIAO_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" >
            <Text>Zongmiao, also known as Ancestral Temple, is a place where the Son of Heaven or princes worship their ancestors. "The Book of Rites: The Imperial System" records: "The Son of Heaven has seven temples, the princes have five temples, the doctor has three temples, and the scholar has one temple. There is no temple for the people. Later scholars believe that this record is inferred from the close relatives and clan organization and the temple system in the Qin and Han dynasties of the Warring States period, so it does not conform to the temple system and the close relatives clan system in the Spring and Autumn period of the Western Zhou Dynasty. </Text>
        </Row>

        <Row Tag="LOC_QUARTER_ZHOU_CAIYI_NAME" >
        <Text>Caiyi</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_QUARTER_ZHOU_CAIYI_DESCRIPTION" >
        <Text>Zhou Unique Quarter. Created by constructing the "Bi Yong" and "Zong Miao" in the same District. +1[icon:YIELD_CULTURE] Culture from Specialists in this City.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_QUARTER_ZHOU_CAIYI_TOOLTIP" >
        <Text>+1[icon:YIELD_CULTURE] Culture from Specialists in this City.</Text>
        </Row>

        <Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_PAGE_QUARTER_ZHOU_CAIYI_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" >
        <Text>The feudal princes of the Western Zhou royal family were different from those inside and outside of Wangji, and the princes who were enshrined in Wangji owned the caiyi, which was the vassal state within Wangji. Those that were enclosed outside Wangji were called vassal states, which served as a barrier to guard the Zhou royal family. Although there are differences in the objects, nature, rights and obligations of the fiefdom and the feudal state, they are all important parts of the Western Zhou feudal system.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_PAGE_QUARTER_ZHOU_CAIYI_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_2" >
        <Text>From the late Western Zhou Dynasty to the early Spring and Autumn Period, the Zhou royal family declined, and the princes and powers greatly increased their territories through annexation and expansion.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_PAGE_QUARTER_ZHOU_CAIYI_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_3" >
        <Text>After the Qin Dynasty unified China, the county system was established, and the main people who accepted the title were meritorious heroes. The size of the fief is calculated according to the number of households, and it is hereditary by the eldest son.</Text>
        </Row>

        <!-- rivers -->
        <Row Tag="LOC_RIVER_ZHOU_JING_NAME" >
        <Text>Jing River</Text>
        </Row>  
        <Row Tag="LOC_RIVER_ZHOU_WEI_NAME" >
        <Text>Wei River</Text>
        </Row>  

        <!-- units -->
        <Row Tag="LOC_UNIT_ZHOU_CHARIOT_NAME" >
            <Text>Yuanrong chariot</Text>
        </Row>    
        <Row Tag="LOC_UNIT_ZHOU_CHARIOT_BASE_DESCRIPTION" >
            <Text>Zhou Unique Cavalry Unit. Higher Movement. +5 Combat Strength against Independents. Ignores Zone of Control.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_UNIT_ZHOU_CHARIOT_DESCRIPTION" >
            <Text>Tier 2 Zhou Unique Cavalry Unit. Higher Movement. +5 Combat Strength against Independents. Ignores Zone of Control.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_UNIT_ZHOU_CHARIOT_2_DESCRIPTION" >
            <Text>Tier 3 Zhou Unique Cavalry Unit. Higher Movement. +5 Combat Strength against Independents. Ignores Zone of Control.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_PAGE_UNIT_ZHOU_CHARIOT_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" >
            <Text>During the Zhou Dynasty, chariots pulled by horses became the leading force on battlefields, and the strength of each vassal state was counted in terms of how many chariots they controlled. Chariot battles were also common in the poems of the Zhou Dynasty. In "Xiao Ya - June" of the Classic of Poetry, the Zhou army used yuanrong chariots to defeat the Xianyun tribes invading from the north.</Text>
        </Row>

        <Row Tag="LOC_ABILITY_ZHOU_CHARIOT_NAME" >
        <Text>Resist foreign invasions</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_ABILITY_ZHOU_CHARIOT_DESCRIPTION" >
        <Text>+5 Combat Strength against Independents.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_ABILITY_ZHOU_CHARIOT_PREVIEW" >
        <Text>{1_Value} Combat Strength against Independents.</Text>
        </Row>

        <Row Tag="LOC_ABILITY_NARRATIVE_STRENGTH_ZHOU_THINKER_SUN_WU_NAME" >
        <Text>Sun Wu ruled the army</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_ABILITY_NARRATIVE_STRENGTH_ZHOU_THINKER_SUN_WU_DESCRIPTION" >
        <Text>+3 Combat Strength</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_ABILITY_NARRATIVE_STRENGTH_ZHOU_THINKER_SUN_WU_PREVIEW" >
        <Text>+{1_Amount} from Sun Wu</Text>
        </Row>
        

        <Row Tag="LOC_UNIT_ZHOU_THINKER_NAME" >
        <Text>Thinker of Zhou</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_UNIT_ZHOU_THINKER_DESCRIPTION" >
        <Text>A Great Person with one charge. Can only be trained in Cities with a Library, and the specific Thinker received is random. Each Thinker can only be received once. Cost increases per Thinker trained.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_PAGE_UNIT_ZHOU_THINKER_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" >
        <Text>Zhuzi refers to the representatives of academic thought such as Guanzi, Confucius, Mozi, Laozi, Zhuangzi, Mencius, and Xunzi in the pre-Qin period of China; The hundred schools of thought refer to the representatives of various academic schools such as Confucianism, Taoism, Moism, Mingjia, and Legalism. In the late Spring and Autumn Period, there were different schools of thought such as Legalism, Taoism, Confucianism, Moism, and Yin-Yang School, which had considerable social influence, and by the middle of the Warring States Period, many schools of thought were numerous, and many theories were rich and colorful, laying a broad foundation for the development of Chinese culture.</Text>
        </Row>

        <!-- copy from han great people -->
        <Row Tag="LOC_GREAT_PERSON_INDIVIDUAL_ZHOU_THINKER_LAOZI_NAME" >
        <Text>{LOC_GREAT_PERSON_INDIVIDUAL_SHI_DAFU_LAOZI_NAME}</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_GREATWORK_LAOZI_TAO_ZHOU_NAME" >
        <Text>{LOC_GREATWORK_LAOZI_TAO_NAME}</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_GREATWORK_LAOZI_TAO_ZHOU_DESCRIPTION" >
        <Text>+2 Happiness</Text>
        </Row>

        <Row Tag="LOC_GREAT_PERSON_INDIVIDUAL_ZHOU_THINKER_MENCIUS_NAME" >
        <Text>{LOC_GREAT_PERSON_INDIVIDUAL_SHI_DAFU_MENCIUS_NAME}</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_GREAT_PERSON_INDIVIDUAL_ZHOU_THINKER_MENCIUS_DESCRIPTION" >
        <Text>{LOC_GREAT_PERSON_INDIVIDUAL_SHI_DAFU_MENCIUS_DESCRIPTION}</Text>
        </Row>

        <Row Tag="LOC_GREAT_PERSON_INDIVIDUAL_ZHOU_THINKER_MOZI_NAME" >
        <Text>{LOC_GREAT_PERSON_INDIVIDUAL_SHI_DAFU_MOZI_NAME}</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_GREAT_PERSON_INDIVIDUAL_ZHOU_THINKER_MOZI_DESCRIPTION" >
        <Text>{LOC_GREAT_PERSON_INDIVIDUAL_SHI_DAFU_MOZI_DESCRIPTION}</Text>
        </Row>

        <Row Tag="LOC_GREAT_PERSON_INDIVIDUAL_ZHOU_THINKER_SHANG_YANG_NAME" >
            <Text>{LOC_GREAT_PERSON_INDIVIDUAL_SHI_DAFU_SHANG_YANG_NAME}</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_GREAT_PERSON_INDIVIDUAL_ZHOU_THINKER_SHANG_YANG_DESCRIPTION" >
            <Text>{LOC_GREAT_PERSON_INDIVIDUAL_SHI_DAFU_SHANG_YANG_DESCRIPTION}</Text>
        </Row>

        <!-- new great people -->
        <Row Tag="LOC_GREAT_PERSON_INDIVIDUAL_ZHOU_THINKER_GONGSUN_LONG_NAME" >
            <Text>Gongsun Long</Text>
        </Row>

        <Row Tag="LOC_GREATWORK_GONGSUN_LONG_GSLZ_ZHOU_NAME" >
            <Text>Gongsun Long Zi</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_GREATWORK_GONGSUN_LONG_GSLZ_ZHOU_DESCRIPTION" >
            <Text>+2 Culture</Text>
        </Row>

        <Row Tag="LOC_GREAT_PERSON_INDIVIDUAL_ZHOU_THINKER_ZOU_YAN_NAME" >
            <Text>Zou Yan</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_GREAT_PERSON_INDIVIDUAL_ZHOU_THINKER_ZOU_YAN_DESCRIPTION" >
            <Text>Activate on a Library to add +3[icon:YIELD_CULTURE] Culture to the Building.</Text>
        </Row>

        <Row Tag="LOC_GREAT_PERSON_INDIVIDUAL_ZHOU_THINKER_GUIGUZI_NAME" >
            <Text>Guiguzi</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_GREAT_PERSON_INDIVIDUAL_ZHOU_THINKER_GUIGUZI_DESCRIPTION" >
            <Text>Activate on a Library, to immediately gain 150[icon:YIELD_DIPLOMACY] Diplomacy. (On Standard Speed)</Text>
        </Row>

        <Row Tag="LOC_GREAT_PERSON_INDIVIDUAL_ZHOU_THINKER_LV_BUWEI_NAME" >
            <Text>Lü Buwei</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_GREAT_PERSON_INDIVIDUAL_ZHOU_THINKER_LV_BUWEI_DESCRIPTION" >
            <Text>Activate on a Palace to add +6[icon:YIELD_GOLD] Gold to the Building.</Text>
        </Row>

        <Row Tag="LOC_GREAT_PERSON_INDIVIDUAL_ZHOU_THINKER_XU_XING_NAME" >
            <Text>Xu Xing</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_GREAT_PERSON_INDIVIDUAL_ZHOU_THINKER_XU_XING_DESCRIPTION" >
            <Text>Activate in a City Center to add +2[icon:YIELD_FOOD] Food for all Rural Tiles in the City.</Text>
        </Row>

        <Row Tag="LOC_GREAT_PERSON_INDIVIDUAL_ZHOU_THINKER_SUN_WU_NAME" >
        <Text>Sun Wu</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_GREAT_PERSON_INDIVIDUAL_ZHOU_THINKER_SUN_WU_DESCRIPTION" >
        <Text>Activate on an Army Commander to grant it 1 free Promotion.</Text>
        </Row>
        


        <!-- civics -->
        <Row Tag="LOC_TREE_CIVICS_AQ_ZHOU_CHINA_NAME" >
        <Text>Zhou Civics</Text>
        </Row>

        <Row Tag="LOC_CIVIC_FEN_FENG_NAME" >
        <Text>Enfeoffment System</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_CIVIC_FEN_FENG_QUOTE" >
        <Text>Choose moral people, grant them fiefdoms, and use them as a barrier to defend the Zhou Dynasty.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_CIVIC_FEN_FENG_QUOTE_AUTHOR" >
        <Text>Commentary of Zuo</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_PAGE_NODE_CIVIC_AQ_ZHOU_FEN_FENG_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" >
        <Text>The Enfeoffment System was the political system of the Western Zhou Dynasty, and its purpose was to consolidate the rule of the Zhou dynasty. The objects of the enfeoffment included the royal family, meritorious officials, and the nobles of the previous generations. The feudal princes were obliged to obey the orders of the king of Zhou, to contribute money and goods to the king of Zhou, and to send troops to fight with the king of Zhou. The Enfeoffment System consolidated the rule of the Western Zhou Dynasty and expanded its territory.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_PAGE_NODE_CIVIC_AQ_ZHOU_FEN_FENG_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_2" >
        <Text>The Hashtag-shaped-field System (Jingtian System in Chinese) was the state-owned land system in the Western Zhou Dynasty of China, which began to be implemented in the Shang Dynasty, prevailed in the Western Zhou Dynasty, collapsed in the Spring and Autumn Period, and was abolished in the Warring States Period. The ownership of the land in Jingtian belonged to the king of Zhou, who gave the land to the princes and ministers, but the ministers could only enjoy it for generations, and could not be transferred and bought and sold freely, and they had to pay a certain tribute. The Jingtian system is the economic foundation of the Enfeoffment System system, and the Enfeoffment System is the superstructure that adapts to it.</Text>
        </Row>

        <Row Tag="LOC_CIVIC_ZONG_FA_NAME" >
        <Text>Zongfa System</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_CIVIC_ZONG_FA_QUOTE" >
        <Text>If the son of a righteous wife is appointed as the king, he shall be based only on the elderly, not on the basis of wisdom; If the son born of a concubine is appointed king, it is only on the basis of honor, not on the basis of the old.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_CIVIC_ZONG_FA_QUOTE_AUTHOR" >
        <Text>Gongyangzhuan</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_PAGE_NODE_CIVIC_AQ_ZHOU_ZONG_FA_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" >
        <Text>The Zongfa system is a system that upholds the hereditary rule of the aristocracy in ancient times. It evolved from the patriarchal system of the clan society, and was a system in which the royal nobles distributed state power according to blood relations in order to establish hereditary rule. It is characterized by the integration of the clan organization and the state organization, and the complete unity of the patriarchal and political hierarchies.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_PAGE_NODE_CIVIC_AQ_ZHOU_ZONG_FA_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_2" >
        <Text>This system was established in the Xia Dynasty, developed in the Shang Dynasty, completed in the Zhou Dynasty, and influenced later dynasties. According to the patriarchal system of the Zhou Dynasty, the clans were divided into large and small clans. King Zhou called himself the Son of Heaven and was known as the great sect of the world. The sons of the Son of Heaven other than the eldest son were made princes. The princes were small sects to the Son of Heaven, but they were large sects in his fiefdoms. The other sons of the princes were given the title of princes. Doctor Qing was a small sect to the princes, but he was a large sect in his estate. The same is true from doctors to scholars. Therefore, the eldest son of the nobles is always a large clan (zongzi) of different ranks. The Great Sect not only enjoyed the right to rule over the members of the clan, but also enjoyed political privileges. Later, the rulers of various dynasties reformed the patriarchal system and gradually established a feudal patriarchal system composed of political power, clan power, divine power, and husband power.</Text>
        </Row>

        <Row Tag="LOC_CIVIC_LI_YUE_NAME" >
        <Text>Rites and Music Principals</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_CIVIC_LI_YUE_QUOTE" >
        <Text>To make rituals is to trace back to the origin of rituals, and to make music is to express joy at the completion of rituals. The kings of the past instituted rituals that regulated people's behavior; And the music is to guide people's emotions. Therefore, if you look at the ritual music of a country, you can know whether it is orderly or chaotic.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_CIVIC_LI_YUE_QUOTE_AUTHOR" >
        <Text>Book of Rites</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_PAGE_NODE_CIVIC_AQ_ZHOU_LI_YUE_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" >
        <Text>The ritual music system is the concentrated embodiment of the culture of the Zhou Dynasty, which is not only the sum of the code system, but also the code of people's various behaviors. After King Wu of Zhou destroyed the Shang Dynasty, the rulers of the Western Zhou Dynasty established a stable political system in order to consolidate their rule and establish a stable political system, and there were four major systems that supported the Zhou Dynasty: the Enfeoffment System, the Hashtag-shaped-field System, the Zongfa system, and the Rites and Music Principals.</Text>
        </Row>

        <Row Tag="LOC_CIVIC_BAI_JIA_ZHENG_MING_NAME" >
        <Text>Blooming and Contending</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_CIVIC_BAI_JIA_ZHENG_MING_QUOTE" >
        <Text>There are ten factions in Zhuzi, of which only nine are worth watching. They all started after the royal politics had declined, and the princes fought each other by force, and the monarchs at that time liked and disliked differently, so the academics of the nine schools rose one after another. Each of them quoted one of their doctrines, admired the benefits of their doctrines, and used it to lobby and cater to the psychology of the princes.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_CIVIC_BAI_JIA_ZHENG_MING_QUOTE_AUTHOR" >
        <Text>Book of Han</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_PAGE_NODE_CIVIC_AQ_ZHOU_BAI_JIA_ZHENG_MING_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" >
        <Text>During the Spring and Autumn Period and the Warring States Period, society changed dramatically, and many problems needed to be solved urgently. In the Warring States Period, various schools of thought were produced in society, such as Confucianism, Law, Taoism, Mo, etc., they wrote books and lectures, debated with each other, and there was a flourishing scene in academics, which was called a hundred schools of thought in later generations.</Text>
        </Row>

        <Row Tag="LOC_MOD_AQ_ZHOU_FEN_FENG_SETTLEMENT_CAP_INCREASE_DESCRIPTION" >
        <Text>+2 Settlement Limit.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_MOD_AQ_ZHOU_LI_YUE_CAPITAL_CULTURE_DESCRIPTION" >
        <Text>+10%[icon:YIELD_CULTURE] Culture in the Capital.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_MOD_AQ_ZHOU_BJZM_LIBRARY_DIPLOMACY_YIELD_DESCRIPTION" >
        <Text>The Library provides +1[icon:YIELD_DIPLOMACY] Diplomacy.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_MOD_AQ_ZHOU_BJZM_LIBRARY_SCIENCE_YIELD_DESCRIPTION" >
        <Text>The Library provides +1[icon:YIELD_SCIENCE] Science.</Text>
        </Row>

        <!-- traditions -->
        <Row Tag="LOC_TRADITION_JING_TIAN_NAME" >
        <Text>Hashtag-shaped-field System</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_TRADITION_JING_TIAN_DESCRIPTION" >
        <Text>Farms and Plantations provides +2[icon:YIELD_FOOD] Food and +2[icon:YIELD_GOLD] Gold.</Text>
        </Row>

        <Row Tag="LOC_TRADITION_ZONG_FA_NAME" >
            <Text>Zongfa System</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_TRADITION_ZONG_FA_DESCRIPTION" >
            <Text>Your Capital receives +4%[icon:YIELD_PRODUCTION] Production from each city outside the capital, and receives +4% [icon:YIELD_GOLD] Gold from each town.</Text>
        </Row>
        

        <Row Tag="LOC_TRADITION_ZHU_ZI_BAI_JIA_NAME" >
        <Text>Zhuzi and Hundred Schools of Thoughts</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_TRADITION_ZHU_ZI_BAI_JIA_DESCRIPTION" >
        <Text>+50%[icon:YIELD_PRODUCTION] Production towards training Great Peaple Units.</Text>
        </Row>


        <!-- config -->
        <Row Tag="LOC_CIVILIZATION_ZHOU_CHINA_DESCRIPTION" >
        <Text>Culture Buildings gain a +2[icon:YIELD_CULTURE] Culture and +2[icon:YIELD_HAPPINESS] Happiness Adjacency for Quarters.</Text>
        </Row>

        <Row Tag="LOC_LOADING_CIV_INTRO_TEXT_ZHOU_CHINA" >
        <Text>The Zhou Dynasty (1046 BC – 256 BC) was a dynasty founded by Ji Fa, the Wu King of Zhou, the third slave state in Chinese history after the Shang Dynasty. It is divided into two periods: the Western Zhou Dynasty (1046 BC - 771 BC) and the Eastern Zhou Dynasty (770 BC - 256 BC), with a total of 37 kings in 790 years.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_LOADING_INTRO_ZHOU_CHINA" >
        <Text>The Western Zhou Dynasty was a very critical period in the process of Chinese civilization, and the civilization form characterized by the Enfeoffment System, the Zongfa system, and the Rites and Music Principals, and the state structure of the common rulers of the world with Zhou Tianzi as the core, further strengthened the centralized power system since the Xia and Shang dynasties, and laid a solid foundation for the formation of a unified multi-ethnic state in the Qin and Han dynasties.</Text>
        </Row>

        
        <Row Tag="LOC_UNLOCK_PLAY_AS_ZHOU_CHINA_DESCRIPTION" >
        <Text>Play as [B]Zhou[/B].</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_UNLOCK_PLAY_AS_ZHOU_CHINA_MING_TOOLTIP" >
        <Text>[B]Zhou[/B] was a precursor Civilization to [B]Ming[/B].</Text>
        </Row>
        
        <!-- story -->
        <Row Tag="LOC_12522A_COMPLETION" >
        <Text>{LOC_8122A_COMPLETION}</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_12522A_STORYTITLE" >
        <Text>{LOC_8122A_STORYTITLE}</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_12522B_DESCRIPTION" >
        <Text>{LOC_8122B_DESCRIPTION}</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_12522B_NAME" >
        <Text>{LOC_8122B_NAME}</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_12522C_DESCRIPTION" >
        <Text>{LOC_8122C_DESCRIPTION}</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_12522C_NAME" >
        <Text>{LOC_8122C_NAME}</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_12523A_COMPLETION" >
        <Text>{LOC_8123A_COMPLETION}</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_12523A_STORYTITLE" >
        <Text>{LOC_8123A_STORYTITLE}</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_12523B_COMPLETION" >
        <Text>{LOC_8123B_COMPLETION}</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_12523B_DESCRIPTION" >
        <Text>{LOC_8123B_DESCRIPTION}</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_12523B_IMPERATIVE" >
        <Text>{LOC_8123B_IMPERATIVE}</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_12523B_NAME" >
        <Text>{LOC_8123B_NAME}</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_12523B_STORYTITLE" >
        <Text>{LOC_8123B_STORYTITLE}</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_12523C_DESCRIPTION" >
        <Text>{LOC_8123C_DESCRIPTION}</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_12523C_NAME" >
        <Text>{LOC_8123C_NAME}</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_12524A_COMPLETION" >
        <Text>{LOC_8124A_COMPLETION}</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_12524A_STORYTITLE" >
        <Text>{LOC_8124A_STORYTITLE}</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_12524B_DESCRIPTION" >
        <Text>{LOC_8124B_DESCRIPTION}</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_12524B_NAME" >
        <Text>{LOC_8124B_NAME}</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_12524C_DESCRIPTION" >
        <Text>{LOC_8124C_DESCRIPTION}</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_12524C_NAME" >
        <Text>{LOC_8124C_NAME}</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_12525A_COMPLETION" >
        <Text>{LOC_8125A_COMPLETION}</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_12525A_STORYTITLE" >
        <Text>{LOC_8125A_STORYTITLE}</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_12525B_DESCRIPTION" >
        <Text>{LOC_8125B_DESCRIPTION}</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_12525B_NAME" >
        <Text>{LOC_8125B_NAME}</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_12525C_DESCRIPTION" >
        <Text>{LOC_8125C_DESCRIPTION}</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_12525C_NAME" >
        <Text>{LOC_8125C_NAME}</Text>
        </Row>

        <!-- new stories -->
        <Row Tag="LOC_12526A_COMPLETION" >
        <Text>A scholar wanted to worship Gongsun Long as a teacher, but questioned his doctrine that "white horses are not horses". Gongsun Long fell into deep thought, how should he reply to this scholar?</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_12526A_STORYTITLE" >
        <Text>White horses are not horses</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_12526B_DESCRIPTION" >
        <Text>Horses provides +4[icon:YIELD_HAPPINESS] Happiness</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_12526B_NAME" >
        <Text>A white horse is certainly not a horse.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_12526C_DESCRIPTION" >
        <Text>Horses provides +4[icon:YIELD_HAPPINESS] Happiness</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_12526C_NAME" >
        <Text>It's a bit impossible for a white horse to be a horse.</Text>
        </Row>

        <Row Tag="LOC_12527A_COMPLETION" >
        <Text>The monarch heard that Zou Yan was good at talking about Tianyan, so he summoned him and sought his knowledge. What kind of knowledge should Zou Yan tell?</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_12527A_STORYTITLE" >
        <Text>Talking about Tianyan</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_12527B_DESCRIPTION" >
        <Text>+1 Scout sight.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_12527B_NAME" >
        <Text>Tell about the doctrine of the nine Zhou (Regions).</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_12527C_DESCRIPTION" >
        <Text>{1_reward}.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_12527C_NAME" >
        <Text>Tell about Yin and Yang and the five elements.</Text>
        </Row>

        <Row Tag="LOC_12528A_COMPLETION" >
        <Text>Guiguzi has a wide range of knowledge. He looked at his students, hesitating what to teach them.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_12528A_STORYTITLE" >
        <Text>Guiguzi is teaching</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_12528B_DESCRIPTION" >
        <Text>+30%[icon:YIELD_DIPLOMACY] Influence towards initiating Endeavors.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_12528B_NAME" >
        <Text>Students should be taught the art of Constructive Alliance (Hezong).</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_12528C_DESCRIPTION" >
        <Text>+30%[icon:YIELD_DIPLOMACY] Influence towards initiating Sanctions.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_12528C_NAME" >
        <Text>Students should be taught the art of Destructive Collaboration (Lianheng).</Text>
        </Row>

        <Row Tag="LOC_12529A_COMPLETION" >
        <Text>When Lü Buwei was out doing business, he met a prince who was a proton, and his keen business sense told him that this nobleman was like a strange commodity that could be hoarded and sold at a high price.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_12529A_STORYTITLE" >
        <Text>Exotic goods can be hoarded for the future</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_12529B_DESCRIPTION" >
        <Text>{1_reward}.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_12529B_NAME" >
        <Text>Conspire with the nobility to do great things.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_12529C_DESCRIPTION" >
        <Text>+20%[icon:YIELD_GOLD] Gold towards purchasing Buildings</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_12529C_NAME" >
        <Text>Let's go back to serious business.</Text>
        </Row>

        <Row Tag="LOC_12530A_COMPLETION" >
        <Text>At the court, a scholar posed a sharp question to Xu Xing - should the monarch have a warehouse for storing grain and a treasury for storing money? He felt like many pairs of eyes were staring at him.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_12530A_STORYTITLE" >
        <Text>Should a king cultivate the land with the commoners?</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_12530B_COMPLETION" >
        <Text>Although Xu Xing was forced by power, he had to bend his mind to cater to the monarch. But he continued to stand by his own ideas, cultivating the land and calling for fair trade between agricultural products and other commodities.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_12530B_DESCRIPTION" >
        <Text>{1_reward}.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_12530B_IMPERATIVE" >
            <Text>Have 2 Granaries within {1_turn_timer}.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_12530B_NAME" >
        <Text>The monarch should have the treasury and the treasury.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_12530B_STORYTITLE" >
        <Text>Flexibility vs persistence</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_12530C_DESCRIPTION" >
        <Text>+10% Growth Rate in all Cities.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_12530C_NAME" >
        <Text>The monarch should personally participate in the cultivation.</Text>
        </Row>

        <Row Tag="LOC_12531A_COMPLETION" >
        <Text>At the request of the monarch, Sun Wu trained the palace maids in the way of the army. He looked at the palace maid in front of him who did not obey orders, should he stick to his principles and execute the two captains, or should he skip this section for the sake of the monarch's favors?</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_12531A_STORYTITLE" >
        <Text>Sun Wu trains female soldiers</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_12531B_DESCRIPTION" >
        <Text>military units +3 Combat Strength.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_12531B_NAME" >
        <Text>The army should enforce orders and prohibitions, and reward and punish them clearly.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_12531C_DESCRIPTION" >
        <Text>{1_reward}.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_12531C_NAME" >
        <Text>Pardon the palace maids.</Text>
        </Row>

    </EnglishText>
</Database>